Inventory of the James Robert Huntley papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Distribution list
  - October documents, 1977 October (Box-folder 366: 52)
  - October proceedings, 1977 October (Box-folder 366: 53)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box-folder 366: 54)
  - Comments on concept paper by B. Wood, undated (Box-folder 366: 55)
  - Humphrey, Senate Record, 1977 May (Box-folder 366: 56)
  - Participants list, Consortium for Atlantic-Pacific Affairs (CAPA) meeting, 1977 June (Box-folder 366: 57)
  - Feasibility report, Consortium for Atlantic-Pacific Affairs (CAPA), undated (Box-folder 366: 58)
  - Battelle Memorial Institute, annual report, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 366: 59)
  - T-A fund and memo, undated (Box-folder 366: 60)
  - Testimony, undated (Box-folder 366: 61)
  - Proceedings, undated (Box-folder 366: 62)
  - Four-year plan, undated (Box-folder 366: 63)
  - Operations plan, undated (Box-folder 366: 64)
  - Consortium for Atlantic-Pacific Affairs (CAPA) program, circa 1977 (Box-folder 366: 65)
  - Battelle Seminar and Study Program/Advanced International Systems, undated (Box-folder 366: 66)
  - Human resources, undated (Box-folder 366: 67)
  - Huntley, Orbis, undated (Box-folder 366: 68)
  - Nomenclature, undated (Box-folder 366: 69)
  - Six color prints, undated (Box-folder 366: 70)
  - Huntley biography, undated (Box-folder 366: 71-72)
  - Consortium for Atlantic-Pacific Affairs (CAPA) articles of incorporation and by laws, undated (Box-folder 366: 73)
  - Invitees list, lunch, undated (Box-folder 366: 74)
  - Invitees list, meeting, undated (Box-folder 366: 75)
  - World Affairs Council study report, 1977 October (Box-folder 366: 76)
  - Working paper, Consortium for Atlantic-Pacific Affairs (CAPA) Curriculum Conference, 1978 February (Box-folder 366: 77)
  - "The Theory Behind CAPA,", 1978 March (Box-folder 366: 78)
  - Consortium for Atlantic-Pacific Affairs (CAPA) program, 1978 March (Box-folder 366: 79)
  - Key people and short history, Consortium for Atlantic-Pacific Affairs (CAPA), 1978 March (Box-folder 366: 80)
  - "Plan for First CAPA Senior Briefing,", 1978 February (Box-folder 366: 81)
  - One-page program paper, undated (Box-folder 366: 82)
  - "This Is Battelle," booklet, undated (Box-folder 366: 83)
  - Battelle Annual Report, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 366: 84)
- Memoirs, plans, tasks, and schedule, 2005 (Box-folder 366: 85)
- Committees for a Community of Democracies task force, 2008 November (Box-folder 367: 1)
- League of Democracies, background, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 367: 2)
- Chronology, 2005 (Box-folder 367: 3-4)
- US-Russian relations, 2007 (Box-folder 367: 5)
- Chronology, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 368: 1-2)
- UN Caucus of Democracies, 2003-2006 (Box-folder 368: 3)
- A/P Affairs Annals, 1984-1990 (Box-folder 368: 4)
- United Way, 1983 (Box-folder 368: 5)
- Once & Future West, Huntley, 1985 (Box-folder 368: 6)
- Miscellaneous (Box-folder 368: 7)
- Essential clippings, 1980-2008 (Box-folder 369: 1-5)
- Essential clippings, 2004-2008 (Box-folder 370: 1-2)
- Democratic peace, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 370: 3)
  Includes DVD.
- Living on the Peninsula, magazine, 2009 (Box-folder 370: 4)
- Photographs, 1950s, 1968, 1979 (Box-folder 370: 5-6)
- The NATO Story, 1949-1965 (Box-folder 370: 7-8)
- The NATO Story, photographs, 1965 July (Box-folder 370: 9)
- Atlantic Council of the United States, correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 370: 10)
- Battelle business correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 370: 11)